Eduardo Elías Chacón

Web Developer

Buenos Aires, Argentina | +54 9 11 33564337 | eduardo.elias.1192@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/eduardoe92/ | https://eduardoeliaschacon-portfolio.vercel.app/

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE:

Full Stack Developer with experience in designing, developing and maintaining web applications. Working on projects covering both Front-end and Back-end, standing out in the implementation of efficient solutions and the optimization of the user experience. My experience includes the creation of mobile-first applications and the integration of APIs, with a focus on quality, problem solving and continuous improvement. With a solid technical background and passion for innovation, committed to delivering exceptional results and adapting to new technologies to contribute to the success of challenging projects.

EDUCATION:

FULL STACK DEVELOPER CORE | OCT 2023 - MAY 2024 | DIGITAL NAO X TECMILENIO

- Development and optimization of user interfaces and systems in the Front-end, using modern technologies to ensure a fluid and attractive user experience.
- · Implementation of logic, server management and database management in the Back-end, ensuring the integrity and efficiency of the applications.

DEVELOPER FULL STACK | DEC 2022 - SEPT 2023 | EGG COOPERATION

- Acquisition of programming and development skills with Java, MySQL databases and React.js, focusing on the creation
 of robust and scalable solutions.
- Application of object-oriented programming principles, exception handling and establishment of database connections to improve the functionality and stability of the software.

WEB DEVELOPER FRONT END | MARCH 2022 - JUNE 2023 | EIDOS GLOBAL - ACCENTURE

- · Develop advanced skills in Front-end technologies to improve the creation and design of user interfaces.
- Implement solutions using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Bootstrap, and manage code versions with GitHub to ensure efficient and organized delivery of projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

DEVELOPER FRONT END | IGROWKER | JUNE 2024 - JULY 2024

- Developed the layout of a mobile-first web application for efficient event management, ensuring an intuitive interface and an optimized user experience on mobile devices.
- Validated the technical and commercial viability of the project, contributing to its success and facilitating the professional growth of the development team through innovative and practical solutions.

DEVELOPER FRONT END | MAKISAN TECH | JUNE 2023 - DEC 2024

- Development and maintenance of applications and websites, ensuring the quality and continued functionality of the products.
- İmproving the user experience and optimizing project performance by implementing best development practices and advanced optimization techniques.

TECHNICAL KNOWLEDGE:

Java | React JS | Java Script | Astro | Node JS | Spring MVC | OOP | RESTful APIs | Bootstrap | Tailwind | MySQL | HTML | CSS | GitHub | Vercel | Figma | Postman | Wordpress | Trello | Notion | Miro | Vercel.

SKILL SET:

Agile | Systems Management | Process Optimization | Customer Service | Quality Control | Technical Support | Effective Communication | Adaptability | Attention to Details | Time Management | Creativity | Logical and Analytical Thinking | Teamwork.

LANGUAJES:

- · Spanish: Native.
- · English: A1-A2.